[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What scale is used by astronomers to rate the potential hazard of impact of a near-earth object?", "correct_answer": "Palermo Technical Impact Hazard Scale", "incorrect_answers": ["Boston Impact Hazard Scale", "Genoa Technical Impact Hazard Scale", "Urbino Impact Hazard Scale"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What happened to the first prototype of the bread-slicing machine?", "correct_answer": "It was destroyed in a fire.", "incorrect_answers": ["It was destroyed by its inventor.", "It was stolen by the people of Battle Creek, Michigan.", "It was destroyed by vandals."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The only thing taken from the Indian Village where Indiana and Co. end up in Indiana Jones and the Temple of Doom is a missing Sacred Stone.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who does Gabriel marry in the 2000 movie The Patriot?", "correct_answer": "Anne Howard", "incorrect_answers": ["Margaret Martin", "Anne McFisher", "Susan Tavington"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A lightning bolt can produce what voltage?", "correct_answer": "1 billion volts", "incorrect_answers": ["4 million volts", "400 million volts", "1 million volts"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many bones is an adults human skeletal system made up of?", "correct_answer": "206", "incorrect_answers": ["132", "318", "354"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Michael Madsen, Uma Thurman, Vivica Fox and Samuel L. Jackson were in Kill Bill and Kill Bill vol. II.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the state fish of Colorado?", "correct_answer": "Greenback Cutthroat Trout", "incorrect_answers": ["Rainbow Trout", "Walleye", "Salmon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Bernard Webb was a pseudonym used by which famous musician and songwriter?", "correct_answer": "Paul McCartney", "incorrect_answers": ["John  Lennon", "Peter Asher", "none of these  three answers is  correct"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does this equation describe?  y=A(sin) wt, where A is the amplitude and t is the time.", "correct_answer": "Simple harmonic motion", "incorrect_answers": ["The tangent of the angle x", "The cosine of the angle w", "Linear motion"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The panda is the symbol of this conservation organization, formed in 1961.", "correct_answer": "The World Wildlife Fund", "incorrect_answers": ["Leave It Wild", "The Conservation Society", "The African Conservation Foundation"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the meaning of the Italian word riavvolgere, from which the name of the popular Italian dish ravioli originated?", "correct_answer": "To wrap", "incorrect_answers": ["Poor peasant", "Onion", "To indulge"]}]